/* jshint esversion: 6 */
/* jshint -W033 */

// Questions - 1989
export const nineteeneightynineQuestions = [
    {
    "question": "The lights are so bright, but they never blind me",
    "answers": ["Blank Space", "Wildest Dreams", "Welcome to New York", "Style"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "Oh my God, look at that face, you look like my next mistake",
    "answers": ["This Love", "Blank Space", "Wonderland", "Clean"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "You got that long hair, slicked back, white t-shirt",
    "answers": ["Style", "Bad Blood", "Wildest Dreams", "Shake it Off"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "Remember when you hit the brakes too soon? Twenty stitches in a hospital room",
    "answers": ["This Love", "Clean", "Out of the Woods", "You Are in Love"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "'Cause the players gonna play, play, play, play, play ",
    "answers": ["Shake it Off", "I Wish You Would", "Out of the Woods", "New Romantics"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "I'd never forget you as long as I'd live",
    "answers": ["Bad Blood", "Wonderland", "Clean", "I Wish You Would"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "Still got scars on my back from your knife",
    "answers": ["Welcome to New York", "Bad Blood", "Blank Space", "Clean"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "Say you'll remember me, standing in a nice dress staring at the sunset, babe",
    "answers": ["Wildest Dreams", "This Love", "Shake it Off", "Wonderland"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "Broke your heart, I'll put it back together",
    "answers": ["Clean", "Shake it Off", "Style", "How You Get the Girl"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "Skies grew darker, currents swept you out again",
    "answers": ["Wonderland", "This Love", "Blank Space", "Clean"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "Just grab my hand and don't ever drop it",
    "answers": ["I Know Places", "This Love", "New Romantics", "Bad Blood"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "Let the flood carry away all my pictures of you",
    "answers": ["Blank Space", "Clean", "Shake it Off", "Wonderland"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "Didn't they tell us don't rush into things?",
    "answers": ["Wonderland", "New Romantics", "This Love", "Shake it Off"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "You two are dancing in a snow globe, 'round and 'round",
    "answers": ["Clean", "Blank Space", "You Are in Love", "Bad Blood"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "Heartbreak is the national anthem",
    "answers": ["New Romantics", "Style", "Bad Blood", "Clean"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "Cherry lips, crystal skies I could show you incredible things",
    "answers": ["Welcome to New York", "Clean", "Shake it Off", "Blank Space"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "You got that James Dean daydream look in your eye",
    "answers": ["I Know Places", "Style", "Shake it Off", "Bad Blood"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "I go on too many dates, but I can't make 'em stay",
    "answers": ["Shake it Off", "Bad Blood", "Clean", "You Are in Love"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "They are the hunters, we are the foxes",
    "answers": ["New Romantics", "Blank Space", "Style", "I Know Places"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "It's all fun and games 'til somebody loses their mind",
    "answers": ["Wonderland", "This Love", "Clean", "You Are in Love"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "You can hear it in the silence",
    "answers": ["Clean", "You Are in Love", "I Know Places", "Style"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "'Cause baby, I could build a castle out of all the bricks they threw at me",
    "answers": ["Wildest Dreams", "Shake it Off", "Blank Space", "New Romantics"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "The rest of the world was black and white, but we were in screaming color",
    "answers": ["Out of the Woods", "Bad Blood", "This Love", "Clean"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "Remind me how it used to be, pictures in frames of kisses on cheeks ",
    "answers": ["Wonderland", "How You Get the Girl", "Blank Space", "Style"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "When the flowers that we'd grown together died of thirst",
    "answers": ["Clean", "Style", "Wonderland", "Bad Blood"],
    "correct": 0
    }
];